( Watch on www.kissasia.co, .be, .org, .net, .id, .xyz )
(شاهد على www.kissasia.co، .be، .org، .net، .id، .xyz)
I really do not know what to do with you.
لا أعرف حقاً ماذا أفعل بك.
Is that enough?
هل هذا يكفي؟
Go to sleep. Good night.
نم نوماً هنيئاً. ليلة سعيدة.
All right. You are blocking my view.
حسناً. أنت تحجب رؤيتي.
Go to sleep. Do not get in the way.
اذهب للنوم. لا تعيق طريقك.
Sleeping is what matters right now.
النوم هو الأهم الآن.
♪Hey, don't plan too far ahead♪
♪مهلاً، لا تخطط للمستقبل البعيد♪
♪The next second might change everything♪
♪ قد تُغير الثانية التالية كل شيء ♪
♪Sway along with the music♪
♪تمايل مع الموسيقى♪
♪Off-key becomes a romantic beat♪
♪يتحول النشاز إلى إيقاع رومانسي♪
♪It's showtime♪
حان وقت العرض!
♪Falling into the unknown♪
♪السقوط في المجهول♪
♪Tonight♪
♪الليلة♪
♪I put on a masquerade mask♪
♪ارتديت قناعًا تنكريًا♪
♪Looking at you♪
♪ أنظر إليك ♪
♪You remind me of a romance film♪
♪أنتِ تُذكرينني بفيلم رومانسي♪
♪All night long♪
♪طوال الليل♪
♪From sea to shore♪
♪من البحر إلى الشاطئ♪
♪A fate bound to fall♪
♪مصير محتوم♪
♪Into the light♪
♪إلى النور♪
♪Lost in a captivating opera♪
♪ضائع في أوبرا آسرة♪
♪Frozen within♪
♪متجمد من الداخل♪
I am not ready yet
لستُ مستعداً بعد
to form a pact.
لعقد اتفاق.
When I say sleep,
عندما أقول النوم،
I mean sleep, literally.
أقصد النوم، حرفياً.
[SPECIAL ADMINISTRATION]
[إدارة خاصة]
Sorry. You were one step too late.
معذرةً، لقد تأخرت خطوةً واحدة.
The fragment has already been sold.
تم بيع القطعة بالفعل.
I found it.
لقد وجدته.
Around six last night,
حوالي الساعة السادسة من الليلة الماضية،
Yin Che sent out a same-city delivery.
أرسل يين تشي طلبية توصيل داخل نفس المدينة.
The item description notes
ملاحظات وصف المنتج
fragile glass.
زجاج هش.
That should be the fragment.
ينبغي أن يكون هذا هو الجزء.
Who was it sent to?
إلى من أُرسلت؟
The recipient listed in the shipment record is
المستلم المذكور في سجل الشحنة هو
Wu Nongyu.
وو نونجيو.
[Logistics Tracking Platform]
[منصة تتبع الخدمات اللوجستية]
[Sender: Yin Che. Recipient: Wu Nongyu]
[المرسل: يين تشي. المستلم: وو نونجيو]
If Director Xia finds out
إذا اكتشف المدير شيا ذلك
that Wu Nongyu is looking for fragments,
أن وو نونغيو يبحث عن شظايا،
Nongyu will be in danger.
سيكون نونغيو في خطر.
We still do not know why she is collecting the fragments.
ما زلنا لا نعرف سبب قيامها بجمع الشظايا.
We can only find a way
لا يسعنا إلا إيجاد حل
to quietly take it from her first.
أن آخذها منها بهدوء أولاً.
I can sneak in and steal it.
يمكنني التسلل وسرقته.
Tonight,
الليلة،
you come with me to Nongyu's place for dinner.
تعال معي إلى منزل نونغيو لتناول العشاء.
We will look for a chance to make a move.
سنبحث عن فرصة للقيام بخطوة.
Then me...
ثم أنا...
I am basically the extra one here?
أنا ببساطة الشخص الزائد هنا؟
I have a more important task for you.
لدي مهمة أكثر أهمية لك.
Director Xia said
قال المدير شيا
the third fragment is in Mugang.
الجزء الثالث موجود في موغانغ.
You go.
اذهب أنت.
Does this count as
هل يُعتبر هذا بمثابة
a double date?
موعد غرامي مزدوج؟
I just finished up some work,
انتهيت للتو من بعض الأعمال،
happened to be nearby,
تصادف وجودي في مكان قريب،
so I stopped by.
لذا مررت من هنا.
My hands feel a little dry.
أشعر بجفاف طفيف في يديّ.
Do you have hand cream?
هل لديكِ كريم لليدين؟
It is in my bedroom.
إنه في غرفة نومي.
I will get it for you.
سأحضره لك.
I can get it myself.
أستطيع الحصول عليه بنفسي.
I do not need anyone to serve me.
لست بحاجة إلى أحد ليخدمني.
Did you hear that? She means you.
هل سمعت ذلك؟ إنها تقصدك أنت.
I am going to the restroom.
سأذهب إلى دورة المياه.
What are you doing?
ماذا تفعل؟
I am sorry.
أنا آسف.
I was just about to find it.
كنت على وشك العثور عليه.
Xie Xinxu showed up out of nowhere
ظهر شي شينكسو فجأة من العدم
and stopped me.
وأوقفني.
♪City lights, hazy lines♪
أضواء المدينة، خطوط ضبابية
♪Running into a peculiar kind of crime♪
♪مواجهة نوع غريب من الجرائم♪
♪Accomplices in passion♪
♪شركاء في العاطفة♪
♪Shared a sweet damnation♪
♪شاركنا لعنة حلوة♪
♪Shedding the skin, the consequence♪
♪ التخلص من الجلد، والنتيجة ♪
♪Heaven's gates open wide for a time♪
♪تُفتح أبواب السماء على مصراعيها لبعض الوقت♪
♪Once you cross the line of flame♪
♪بمجرد أن تتجاوز خط اللهب♪
♪Watch the game♪
♪شاهد المباراة♪
♪Turn to flames♪
♪تحوّل إلى لهيب♪
♪Just name♪
♪فقط سمِّ♪
I told you to go into his room to get the item.
قلت لك أن تدخل غرفته لتأخذ الغرض.
Did I give you permission to flirt with him?
هل سمحت لكِ بالتغازل معه؟
I hate the smell of another man on you.
أكره رائحة رجل آخر عليكِ.
You are jealous.
أنت تشعر بالغيرة.
You care about me a lot, right?
أنت تهتم بي كثيراً، أليس كذلك؟
You are overthinking it.
أنت تبالغ في التفكير في الأمر.
Then when I used to spend so much time with Lin Juan,
ثم عندما كنت أقضي الكثير من الوقت مع لين جوان،
why did you not react like this?
لماذا لم تتصرف بهذه الطريقة؟
You and Lin Juan are both mine.
أنتِ ولين جوان ملكي.
Why would I be mad?
لماذا سأغضب؟
Got it.
فهمتها.
You are upset just because you
أنت منزعج لمجرد أنك
dislike Xie Xinxu.
أنا لا أحب Xie Xinxu.
Get some rest.
خذ قسطاً من الراحة.
I will head back first.
سأعود أولاً.
It is too late tonight.
لقد فات الأوان الليلة.
Just sleep here.
نم هنا فقط.
Then stay with me.
إذن ابقَ معي.
I still have work to handle.
لا يزال لدي عمل لأنجزه.
You do not need to wait for me.
لستَ بحاجةٍ إلى انتظاري.
Sleep in the guest room tonight.
نم في غرفة الضيوف الليلة.
No.
لا.
Do not touch me.
لا تلمسني.
If you will not go to the guest room, then I will.
إذا لم تذهب إلى غرفة الضيوف، فسأذهب أنا.
Look, you are drooping again.
انظر، لقد بدأت تترهل مرة أخرى.
I am not drooping.
أنا لستُ متدليًا.
Not drooping?
لا تتدلى؟
Let me see.
دعني أرى.
It really is not drooping.
إنها ليست متدلية حقاً.
Is it drooping or not?
هل هو متدلٍ أم لا؟
You tell me. Is it drooping or not?
أخبرني أنت. هل هو متدلٍ أم لا؟
Fine. I admit it.
حسناً. أعترف بذلك.
When I saw you standing so close to Li Xiang today,
عندما رأيتك تقف قريباً جداً من لي شيانغ اليوم،
I...
أنا...
I was just unhappy.
كنتُ غير سعيد فحسب.
I know it was an accident.
أعلم أنه كان حادثاً.
But I was still unhappy.
لكنني كنت لا أزال غير سعيد.
How about now?
ماذا عن الآن؟
Are you happy?
هل أنت سعيد؟
No.
لا.
Still not happy?
ما زلت غير راضٍ؟
Mm.
مم.
Happy now?
هل أنت سعيد الآن؟
No.
لا.
Then...
ثم...
Ms. Wu, give me a chance to make things right.
يا آنسة وو، امنحيني فرصة لتصحيح الأمور.
Go answer the door.
اذهب وافتح الباب.
What is this?
ما هذا؟
No idea. Your package.
لا أعرف. طردك.
Then help me open it.
ثم ساعدني في فتحه.
Okay.
تمام.
Back then, the Special Administration Bureau ignored my wishes
في ذلك الوقت، تجاهل مكتب الإدارة الخاصة رغباتي
and forced me into a secret experiment.
وأجبرني على الخضوع لتجربة سرية.
I barely escaped.
لقد نجوت بأعجوبة.
( Watch on www.kissasia.co, .be, .org, .net, .id, .xyz )
(شاهد على www.kissasia.co، .be، .org، .net، .id، .xyz)
So
لذا
the person who forced you into that experiment before
الشخص الذي أجبرك على خوض تلك التجربة من قبل
was my brother.
كان أخي.
Why did you hide this from me?
لماذا أخفيت هذا عني؟
I don't want what happened between your brother and me
لا أريد أن يحدث ما حدث بيني وبين أخيك
to come between us.
ليقف بيننا.
Wu Siyuan must feel the same way.
لا بد أن وو سييوان يشعر بنفس الشعور.
Can you tell me
هل يمكن أن تخبرني
why my brother carried out that secret experiment?
لماذا أجرى أخي تلك التجربة السرية؟
Sorry.
آسف.
I will go ask my brother myself.
سأذهب وأسأل أخي بنفسي.
Do not follow me.
لا تتبعني.
Wu Siyuan.
وو سيوان.
How much have you been hiding from me?
كم من الأشياء كنت تخفيها عني؟
Fine.
بخير.
I will come clean.
سأعترف بالحقيقة.
The Ren I formed a pact with
عقدت مملكة رين الأولى اتفاقاً مع
was Li Xiang.
كان لي شيانغ.
What else?
ماذا بعد؟
Where did you get this video?
من أين حصلت على هذا الفيديو؟
What you did in that video is no different from abuse.
ما فعلته في ذلك الفيديو لا يختلف عن الإساءة.
Why did you torment him?
لماذا عذبته؟
I was only training his combat ability.
كنت أدرب قدراته القتالية فقط.
Other Ren would kill for that chance.
رين آخر مستعد للقتل من أجل تلك الفرصة.
What is the problem?
ما المشكلة؟
You call that training?
أتسمي هذا تدريباً؟
Then it is fine if I make it public, right?
إذن لا بأس إذا نشرته للعامة، أليس كذلك؟
So you are choosing justice over family?
إذن أنت تختار العدالة على حساب العائلة؟
I am just following your example, Wu Siyuan.
أنا فقط أقتدي بك يا وو سييوان.
Did you not do the same before?
ألم تفعل الشيء نفسه من قبل؟
Dad!
أب!
He has not given up, has he?
لم يستسلم، أليس كذلك؟
It's not like that...
الأمر ليس كذلك...
Mom is already like this.
أمي هكذا بالفعل.
Why is he still dragging you into this
لماذا لا يزال يجرك إلى هذا الأمر؟
and making you suffer for no reason?
وجعلك تعاني بلا سبب؟
He is no longer trustworthy.
لم يعد جديراً بالثقة.
I am reporting this.
أقوم بالإبلاغ عن هذا.
Wu Ming.
وو مينغ.
You have been reported for conducting illegal experiments.
تم الإبلاغ عنك لإجرائك تجارب غير قانونية.
Please cooperate with the investigation.
يرجى التعاون مع التحقيق.
Dad!
أب!
Later,
لاحقاً،
we will go to the hospital and bring Mom home.
سنذهب إلى المستشفى ونعيد أمي إلى المنزل.
Is this Wu Siyuan?
هل هذا وو سييوان؟
Yes.
نعم.
About an hour ago,
قبل حوالي ساعة،
your parents, Wu Ming and Lin Yu,
والديك، وو مينغ ولين يو،
set themselves and their car on fire in the suburbs.
أضرموا النار في أنفسهم وفي سيارتهم في الضواحي.
You need to come to the police station now
يجب عليك الحضور إلى مركز الشرطة الآن
to complete the necessary procedures.
لإتمام الإجراءات اللازمة.
I am sorry.
أنا آسف.
[File Folder. Wu Nongyu]
[ملف. وو نونغيو]
What happened to your father
ماذا حدث لوالدك؟
had too much impact.
كان له تأثير كبير للغاية.
The school cannot withstand the public pressure anymore.
لم تعد المدرسة قادرة على تحمل الضغط الشعبي.
Wu Nongyu
وو نونجيو
cannot continue studying at our school.
لا يمكنني مواصلة الدراسة في مدرستنا.
It is fine.
لا بأس.
They are narrow minded.
إنهم ضيقو الأفق.
We will not stoop to their level.
لن ننحدر إلى مستواهم.
I will take you somewhere else.
سآخذك إلى مكان آخر.
We will start over.
سنبدأ من جديد.
As long as they are Ren,
طالما أنهم رين،
they do not have normal human emotions.
إنهم لا يملكون مشاعر إنسانية طبيعية.
Their greatest value is to be used as weapons.
تكمن قيمتها الكبرى في استخدامها كأسلحة.
Once they are worn out,
بمجرد أن تبلى،
they are discarded.
يتم التخلص منها.
So they do not harm anyone else.
لذلك فهم لا يؤذون أي شخص آخر.
So this is how you see Li Xiang as well?
إذن، هذه هي نظرتك إلى لي شيانغ أيضاً؟
She is just a weapon you cultivated.
إنها مجرد سلاح قمت بتطويره.
A supply you use when you need it.
مورد تستخدمه عند الحاجة إليه.
She could never be your lover.
لا يمكن أن تكون حبيبتك أبداً.
She could never be your wife, right?
لا يمكن أن تكون زوجتك أبداً، أليس كذلك؟
Yes.
نعم.
So I hope
لذا آمل
you see Xie Xinxu the same way.
ترى Xie Xinxu بنفس الطريقة.
You should know by now.
كان ينبغي أن تعرف ذلك الآن.
Xie Xinxu's real purpose in approaching you.
ما هو الهدف الحقيقي من تقرب شي شينكسو منك؟
It was only to get revenge on me.
كان ذلك فقط للانتقام مني.
He will not love you.
لن يحبك.
He only sees you as a hostage to threaten me with.
إنه لا يراكِ إلا كرهينة ليهددني بها.
That is just your assumption.
هذا مجرد افتراض منك.
You only believe what you want to believe.
أنت لا تصدق إلا ما تريد أن تصدقه.
Just like how you believe
تمامًا كما تؤمن
Dad could never love us.
أبي لم يكن ليحبنا أبداً.
Let us lay everything out today.
دعونا نوضح كل شيء اليوم.
Hand over the fragment Yin Che gave you.
سلّم الجزء الذي أعطاك إياه ين تشي.
Stop messing around.
توقف عن العبث.
The Special Administration Bureau has always banned research on that drug.
لطالما حظر مكتب الإدارة الخاصة إجراء البحوث على هذا الدواء.
I will develop a drug to eliminate Affinity.
سأقوم بتطوير دواء للقضاء على الألفة.
For both of us,
بالنسبة لنا نحن الاثنين،
there is no downside, is there?
لا توجد سلبيات، أليس كذلك؟
That drug may not even exist.
قد لا يكون هذا الدواء موجوداً أصلاً.
And there is nothing wrong with our lives right now.
ولا يوجد أي خطأ في حياتنا الآن.
I do not want any more accidents.
لا أريد وقوع المزيد من الحوادث.
I just do not want
أنا فقط لا أريد
our parents' tragedy to repeat itself.
مأساة والدينا تتكرر.
What I want even more
ما أريده أكثر من ذلك
is for us to truly live like ordinary people.
إن هدفنا هو أن نعيش حقاً كأشخاص عاديين.
Director Xia already knows you are collecting fragments.
المدير شيا يعلم بالفعل أنك تجمع شظايا.
I cannot cover for you much longer.
لا أستطيع أن أغطي عليك لفترة أطول.
It is fine.
لا بأس.
I am prepared.
أنا مستعد.
After all,
في النهاية،
this is not the first time you chose justice over family.
ليست هذه المرة الأولى التي تختار فيها العدالة على حساب العائلة.
♪You smell like something strange♪
رائحتك غريبة!
♪Like wood♪
♪مثل الخشب♪
♪Like wine♪
♪مثل النبيذ♪
♪Like the fading rain♪
♪مثل المطر المتلاشي♪
♪It's not a problem I can fix♪
♪ليست مشكلة أستطيع حلها♪
♪Maybe I'm just meant to be your toy♪
♪ربما أنا مجرد لعبة بالنسبة لك♪